watchgmctv.com 2015-09-15

# Privacy Policy - UPtv.com - Uplifting Entertainment – Family Movies, TV Series, Music

Privacy Policy

Effective August 11, 2015

For purposes of this document “Company” is defined as “UP Entertainment”.

Company is committed to respecting your privacy. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information will be treated if it is collected through this web site (the “Site”) by Company. Except as explicitly provided herein, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Company does not own or control, or to people that Company does not employ or manage. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. Any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. If you have any concern about your privacy in connection with this policy, please send a thorough description to [viewerservices@uptv.com](mailto:viewerservices@uptv.com) and we will try to resolve it. Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. You should check this Site frequently to see recent changes in this Site’s Privacy Policy and its Terms of Use.

**1\. What personal information is collected from me?**

The types of personal information collected on our Sites may include, but are not limited to, your name, email address, standard contact information including addresses and phone numbers, transactional information, and financial information such as your credit card or bank account numbers. You also may provide additional information to us when you conduct a search on this Site, place an order for merchandise, complete a questionnaire or an entry form for sweepstakes or contests, and participate in forums and chat rooms or other community features. We may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding, for example, your personal or professional interests, demographics, experiences with the services we provide and contact preferences. Wherever Company collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

**2\. What general information is collected from me?**

Company may gather and collect various types of information that is anonymous, de-identified or otherwise not intended to personally identify you when you visit any of our Sites. A representative, non-exhaustive list of the types of Non-Personally Identifiable Information collected include: network or Internet Protocol address and the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Chrome, Safari, Firefox), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Microsoft Windows or Mac OS), the domain name of your internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Comcast), mobile network, device identifiers, advertising identifiers, the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream of the web pages you visited on this Site and pages viewed before and after you visit this Site including date and time, general location information, and purchase history.

Company analyzes this data for certain trends in statistics, such as which parts of this Site users visit and how long they spend there. In general, we do not link your IP addresses to anything personally identifiable to you. During some visits Company may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. Company gathers and stores certain types of information whenever you use this Site or the services made available hereon (the “Services”). For example, like many web sites, we use cookies and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses this Site. Various third party companies offer utilities that are designed to allow or help you visit and use web sites anonymously; please note, however, that Company may not be able to provide you with a personalized experience on this Site if you choose to utilize any such utilities.

**3\. What information is collected from social media networks?**

When you engage with our content on social networking sites or applications you may allow us to have access to personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information from your social media profile, such as your name, gender, email address, birthday, location, photos, videos and the posts or the “likes” you make.  Third-party social networking sites and services accessible through this Site have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Company has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please review these independent privacy policies and terms of use for a full description on how these third party sites use your information and how you can control what information you share on these sites.

**4\. Who is collecting my information?**

When you are on this Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Company alone, except as provided herein or unless specifically stated otherwise on this Site. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any company other than Company or an agent for Company, you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer by not using that particular service or purchasing those particular goods. Please be aware that advertisers that may have links on this Site may collect personal information about you through the use of cookies, JavaScript, web beacons, and other technologies. Company does not have any control over or access to such technologies that may be used by these advertisers, and the information practices of those sites linked to this Site either through advertisements or other hyperlinks are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Company does not, however, provide any personally identifiable information about you to these advertisers. Company does use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on the Site, and these third-party advertising companies may, directly or indirectly, collect or use general information about user visits to the Site to display advertisements more tailored to a visitor’s interests. If you wish to know more about this practice, or would like to know more about your options, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) website: [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). The NAI is a cooperative of online advertising companies who are committed to responsible practices and consumer protection.

**5\. How is my information used?**

Company will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others without your consent, except as provided in this Privacy Policy. In general, the information you provide will be used to support your customer relationship with Company. We want to help you quickly find information regarding the Services on this Site and alert you to specific offers, updated information, and other new products and Services that are available. We may use the information you provided about yourself to fulfill your requests for programs and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to enforce the legal terms that govern your use of our Site, and/or for the purposes for which you provided the information. Company may also use the information to improve the design or content of our Sites, and to analyze the usage of our Sites or content. Accordingly, we or selected partners approved by us may send you direct mailings or contact you by telephone about our various products and services or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply opt out by the means provided for (if any) in the mailings or by contacting [viewerservices@UPtv.com](mailto:viewerservices@UPtv.com).

When you provide information from your social media account you consent to the use of this information in accordance with our privacy policy statement. When you provide personally identifiable information to us through an application, on our Sites, or on third party social networking sites, it may be publicly viewed by other members of these sites and we cannot prevent further use of the information by third parties.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Company does research on our users’ demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us during your use of this Site. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Aggregated data does not include personally identifiable information. Company may share this aggregated data with others. Company also may combine your information with information we collect or receive from other companies and sources (such as demographic data) to improve and personalize our services.

**6\. With whom does Company share my information?**

Company may share the personal data you provide or the information gathered by Company to any party with your consent or, in any event, to Company subsidiaries, agents, contractors and our business partners. Company also may share information with the following groups:

(a) businesses which Company does not control but with which it engages in co-branded offerings or other transactions,

(b) third-party service providers in order to facilitate the performance of only those functions which are assigned to them, such as order fulfillment, data analysis, marketing assistance, provision of search results and links, credit card payment processing, and customer service, and

(c) entities with which Company may merge or which may acquire all or substantially all of Company’s assets, as customer information likely will be one of the transferred assets.

In addition, if we believe it is necessary, Company may disclose information collected from you in order to: (a) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, and violations of the Terms of Use, (b) respond to legal process, for example, in response to a subpoena or court order, (c) respond to a law enforcement agency’s request, (d) verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Sites and applicable laws and (e) establish or exercise our legal rights, defend against legal claims, and as otherwise required or permitted by law.

Except as provided in this policy or in the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale of all or substantially all of Company’s assets, we will not share any of your information with any third party without your permission.

**7\. How do I access, update or delete my information?**

You can request the individual information that Company has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in your information, remove personal information from Company’s databases and/or update your personal information through your account on this web site or by contacting [viewerservices@UPtv.com](mailto:viewerservices@UPtv.com).

**8\. What else should I know about my privacy?**

Third-party web sites and services accessible through this Site have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of us. Company has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions. Please be careful and responsible online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your information, Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information through the transmission process, and any transmission by you of information is done at your own risk.

**9\. What does “opt out” mean?**

To “opt out” means that you have notified Company that we no longer have permission to use your information for a particular purpose. For example, when we send you information on a new product, you will be given the opportunity to opt out of receiving such information in the future.

**10\. What are cookies and how are they used by Company?**

Internet cookies are small files that may be placed on your hard drive or in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Company may use cookies or similar technologies to (a) remind us of who you are in order to deliver you better service, (b) estimate our audience size by determining repeat usage of the Site which helps us target advertisements based on user interests and behavior, (c) track your progress and entries in promotions, sweepstakes and contests, and (d) measure certain traffic patterns to understand how our users habits are similar or different from one another.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. By not accepting cookies, some pages of this Site may not display properly or you may not be permitted to access certain information on this Site.

**11\. What are web beacons and how are they used by Company?**

When Company sends you newsletters or promotional emails Company may use web beacons, single-pixel gifs, or similar technologies. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on a Site or in an email to monitor user behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a Site or email. Web beacons allow Company to (a) deliver to you more focused email communications and other information by determining whether you have opened or acted upon a promotional email and which links you have clicked on, (b) effectively deliver co-branded services by counting the number of users who have visited certain web pages, and (c) compile aggregated statistics and determine the efficacy of promotions by using web beacons from third parties without allowing such third parties to use web beacons on this Site to collect or access your personal information.

**12\. Children.**

When a child between the ages of 13 to 18 attempts to register on the Site, he or she may register with the consent and involvement of a parent or guardian. Company will not contact children under the age of 18 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent’s permission. Company does not ask a child under the age of 18 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion. Company does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**13\. Security.**

Company uses its best efforts to protect your personal information and, to that end, uses tools such as encryption, passwords, and physical security to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no web site can be absolutely secure. Third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from this Site. Therefore, although Company works very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain absolutely private.

**14\. How does Company respond to Do Not Track signals?**

At this time the Sites on the UP Network do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms which may include do not track instructions. However, you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser settings. You may set your browser to accept all cookies, block certain cookies, require your consent before a cookie is placed in your browser, or block all cookies. Blocking all cookies will affect your online experience and may prevent you from accessing the full features offered on this Site. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.

**15\. Updates and Effective Date**

Visitors will be notified of changes to this privacy policy via prominent language on the UP homepage. The Privacy Policy posted to this Site was updated on July 14, 2015.

**16\. Other legal notices.**

Any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and application of the law of the state of Georgia.
